## YANNI FERNANDA RIBEIRO FRAGA

Location: Vancouver – BC • Email: yanni\_fernanda@hotmail.com • Phone: 236-868-0081

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/yanni-fraga • Page: yannifraga.com

# **Summary**

Perspective and ambitious professional with 5 years of experience in IT Industry, focused on Web Development. Challenge seeker, with can-do attitude and a good interpersonal relationship. Great analytical skills, creative thinking and a passion about innovations and technologies. Works well under pressure, goal-oriented, cares about self-improvement and Company's growth, with main objective to work as a Junior Web Developer.

#### Education

- ❖ Systems Analysis, Faculdade de Tecnologia de Praia Grande, Feb 2011 Aug 2015
- Certificate in IT, Escola Técnica de Praia Grande ETEC PG, Feb 2008 Jul 2009

## **Professional Experience**

\* IT Technician / Web Developer, Faculdade de Tecnologia de Praia Grande

Aug 2013 – Jan 2017

- Maintenance and development of the college website, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SharePoint 2007 and SQL Server.
- Development of the new college website, using HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Bootstrap, jQuery, PHP Laravel and MySQL.
- IT support for students and professors.
- Intern, Praia Grande City Hall

Jul 2011 – Jun 2013

Development of educational games using ActionScript 3.0 and Flash CS5.

## **Skills & Competencies**

- HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP
- ♦ Git, Gulp

- SQL, MySQL
- PhotoShop, Corel Draw

#### **Volunteer Work**

\* Faculdade de Tecnologia de Praia Grande (remote)

May 2017 – present

Development of the college new website.

Free Geek Vancouver

Jun 2017 – present

Dismantle of small equipment.